let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Peacock : India :: Bear : ? ",
        answer: "Russia",
        options: [
            "Australia",
            "America",
            "England",
            "Russia",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Ornithologist : Bird :: Archaeologist : ? ",
        answer: "Archaeology",
        options: ["Islands",
            "Mediators",
            "Archaeology",
            "Aquatic"],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:
            "Paw : Cat :: Hoof : ? ",
        answer: "Horse",
        options: [
            "Lamb",
            "Elephant",
            "Lion",
            "Horse",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:
            "CUP : LIP :: BIRD : ?",
        answer: "Beak",
        options: ["Buss", "Grass", "Forest", "Beak"],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Architect : Building :: Sculptor : ?",
        answer: "Statue",
        options: ["Museum", "Stone", "Chisel", "Statue"],
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Safe : Secure :: Protect : ?",
        answer: "Guard",
        options: ["Lock", "Sure", "Guard", "Conserve"],
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Microphone : Loud :: Microscope : ?",
        answer: "Magnify",
        options: [
            "Elongate",
            "Investigate",
            "Magnify",
            "Examine",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Melt : Liquid :: Freeze : ?",
        answer: "Solid",
        options: ["Ice", "Condense", "Solid", "Force"],
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Peace : Chaos :: Creation : ? ",
        answer: "Destruction",
        options: [
            "Build",
            "Construction",
            "Destruction",
            "Manufacture",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Physician : Treatment :: Judge : ? ",
        answer: "Judgement",
        options: ["Punishment", "Judgement", "Lawyer", "Court"],
    },
];